The greatest superheroes ever unleashed!
StarDog and TurboCat is a animation, comedy, family film directed by Ben Smith.
When vigilante cat, Felix, and loyal canine, Buddy, set out to find Buddy’s lost owner, they
discover not only the power of friendship, but their inner superpowers along the way.
Felix (voice), played by Luke Evans.
Buddy (voice), played by Nick Frost.
Cassidy (voice), played by Gemma Arterton.
Sinclair (voice), played by Bill Nighy.
Bullion (voice), played by Ben Bailey Smith.
Tinker (voice), played by Rachael Louise Miller.
StarDog and TurboCat is a 2019 British animated superhero film produced by Head Gear Films and Screen
Yorkshire and distributed by Kaleidoscope Film Distribution and animated by Red Star 3D.
Originally titled SpaceDog and TurboCat, the film was directed and written by Ben Smith and features the voices of
Nick Frost, Luke Evans, Gemma Arterton, Bill Nighy, Ben Bailey Smith, Charli D'Amelio and Cory English.
It received mixed reviews from critics, who generally approved of the film's
animation but considered the film itself unsophisticated.
The tone is lighthearted.